sofiavergara.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy at Perfumania.com

**_PRIVACY POLICY_**

Last Updated January 20, 2015

Welcome to the Perfumania.com website (“Website”).  This Website is owned and operated by Perfumania.com, Inc. (“Perfumania”).  This Privacy Policy governs your use of the Website and our use of any information you submit or we gather during your use of the Website. 

**Why We Collect User Information**

Perfumania gathers personal information to help improve our products and customer service, to communicate with you, to process your orders, to provide an enhanced and more personalized shopping experience and to inform you, and your gift and message recipients, of special offers and discounts from us, our affiliated brands and selected third parties.

We may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to the Website, new services, and special offers we think you'll be interested in, and to enable you to receive credits for purchases under loyalty or buying programs which you have joined. If you would rather not receive this information, just follow the removal instructions provided. If you suspect any wrong usage of your email address, please email us to [abuse@perfumania.com](mailto:abuse@perfumania.com).

**What Type of Information We Collect**

**(a)        Information You Provide To Us**

**Personal Information and Demographic Information**.  On the Website, we may ask you to provide certain categories of information such as: (1) personally identifiable information, which is information that identifies you personally, such as your first and last name, email address, home address and phone number (“ **Personal Information** ”); and (2) demographic information, such as information about your gender (“ **Demographic Information** ”).  We may collect this information through various forms and in various places on the Website, including, through “contact us” forms, when you sign up for notifications from us, or when you otherwise interact with the Website.  If we combine Demographic Information with the Personal Information we collect directly from you on the Website, we will treat the combined data as Personal Information under

**(b)        Information We Collect and Store as You Access and Use the Site**

In addition to any Personal Information or other information that you choose to submit to us via our Website, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies that automatically (or passively) store or collect certain information whenever you visit or interact with the Site (“ **Usage Information** ”).  This Usage Information may be stored or accessed using a variety of technologies that may be downloaded to your personal computer, laptop, tablet or mobile phone (a “ **Device** ”) whenever you visit or interact with our Website.  Usage Information may be noncidentifying or may be associated with you.  Whenever we associate Usage Information with your Personal Information, we will treat it as Personal Information.  This Usage Information may include:

  * your IP address or other unique identifier (“ **Device Identifier** ”).  A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your Device used to access the Website, and our computers identify your Device by its Device Identifier;
  * your Device functionality (including browser, operating system, hardware, mobile network information);
  * the URL that referred you to our Website;
  * the areas within our Website that you visit and your activities there, including remembering you and your preferences;
  * your Device location;
  * your Device characteristics; and
  * certain other Device data, including the time of day, among other information.

We may use various developed methods and technologies to store or collect Usage Information (“ **Tracking Technologies** ”).  Tracking Technologies may set, change, alter or modify settings or configurations on your Device.  A few of the Tracking Technologies include, without limitation, the following (and subsequent technology and methods later developed):

A "cookie" is a small data file sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer. We use cookies to let us know that you are a prior customer, user or Member and to provide certain features to you. Most web browsers allow you to instruct the browser to prevent the use of cookies. However, if you disable this feature, certain aspects of the Perfumania.com Website, such as the shopping basket, may not function properly. We have relationships with third parties who may receive non-personal information directly from the cookies placed by our Website on your computer to assist in analyzing our business and customers. Our Website also uses a common web technology "called "action tags" (also called single pixel gifts or web beacons) to anonymously track purchase, usage and other web activity information. Action tags (including third party tags) may be used to provide data to third parties for tracking purposes. However, our Web Site does not use action tags to collect or transfer personal information.

Information you provide to us may be collected by us even if an order, registration, or other process is started but not completed. Members may also add to their Address Book the name, address and telephone number of friends or other persons to whom they may wish to send gifts or expressions, and that information also fall sunder this Policy.  Only Members have the right to view and edit the information entered to their Address Book.

**How We Use the Information Collected**

We may use your Personal Information, Demographic Information or Usage Information for various purposes, including:

  * to send you electronic newsletters or to provide you with special offers or promotional and marketing materials on behalf of us or third parties, including to let you know about new products, services or upcoming events;
  * to improve the Website, marketing endeavors or our service offerings;
  * to customize your experience on the Website or to serve you specific content or ads that are relevant to you;
  * to provide customer support;
  * to contact you with regard to your use of the Website and, in our discretion, changes to the Website and/or Website’s policies;
  * to identify your product and service preferences so that you can be informed of new or additional products, services and promotions;
  * for internal business purposes; and
  * for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

**How and When We Disclose Information to Third Parties**

We do not share Personal or Non-Personal Information with third parties, _unless_ : 

**(a)       Administrative and Legal Reasons**.  We may access, use, preserve, transfer and disclose your information (including Device Identifiers and Personal Information) to third parties: (i) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, subpoenas, governmental requests or legal process if in our good faith opinion such is required or permitted by law; (ii) to protect and/or defend the Website’s **_[Terms of Use](http://www.perfumania.com/content/footerlinks3/terms-of-use/content.html)_** or other policies applicable to the Website, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (iii) to protect the safety, rights, property or security of the Website or any third party; and/or (iv) to detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.  Further, we may use IP address or other Device Identifiers, to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with third parties such as copyright owners, internet service providers, wireless service providers and/or law enforcement agencies, including disclosing such information to third parties, all in our discretion, subject to applicable law.  Such disclosures may be carried out without notice to you.

**(b)        Affiliates and Business Transfer**.  We may share your information, including your Device Identifiers and Personal Information, Demographic Information and Usage Information with our parent, subsidiaries and affiliates.  We also reserve the right to disclose and transfer all such information: (i) to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the Website or applicable database; or (ii) in connection with a merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of our interests and/or assets or other corporate change, including, during the course of any due diligence process. 

**Links and Third Party Content**

Perfumania wants you to be aware that when you click on links and/or ad banners that take you to affiliated or third-party web sites, you will be subject to the privacy policies and terms of use for those websites, not ours. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement and user terms whenever using, and prior to providing any personal information to, any other website.

The Website may contain content that is supplied by a third party, and those third parties may collect Usage Information and your Device Identifier when pages from the Site are served to you.  In addition, when you are on the Website you may be directed to other services that are operated and controlled by third parties that we do not control.  We are not responsible for the data collection and privacy practices employed by any of these third parties or their services and they may be tracking you across multiple sites and may be sharing the results of that tracking with us and/or others. 

**How to Change Customer Information and Communications Preferences**

You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us. The Website may allow you to review, correct or update Personal Information, or you may provide updates and changes by contacting us at [customer.service@perfumania.com. ](mailto:customer.service@perfumania.com.)  We will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our then active databases as soon as reasonably practicable.  Please note that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases and that residual data may remain on backup media or for other reasons.  You may cancel or modify our email marketing communications you receive from us by following the instructions contained within our promotional emails. This will not affect subsequent subscriptions and if your opt-out is limited to certain types of emails the opt-out will be so limited. 

**Transfer of Information outside of the United States**

Our Website is operated in the United States and intended for users located in the United States.  If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect, including Personal Information, will be transferred to, and processed, stored and used in the United States.  The data protection laws in the United States may differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your Personal Information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States according to laws of the United States.  By using the Website or providing us with any information, you consent to the transfer to, and processing, usage, sharing and storage of your information, including Personal Information, in the United States as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Underage Users**

The Website is a general audience website and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children younger than the age of thirteen (13) as required by U.S. law.  We will delete any personal information collected that we later determine to be from a user younger than the age of thirteen (13).  If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of thirteen (13) and believe he or she has disclosed personal information to us, please contact us at [customer.service@perfumania.com. ](mailto:customer.service@perfumania.com.)  ** **  

**Security**

We incorporate commercially reasonable safeguards to help protect and secure your Personal Information.  However, no data transmission over the Internet, mobile networks, wireless transmission or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  Please note that we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to us, and you use our Website and provide us with your information at your own risk. When you place orders or access your account information, we use our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which encrypts all information you enter before it is sent over the Internet to us.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy?**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you.  Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy.  However, we will not use your Personal Information in a manner materially different than promised at the time it was collected without your consent.  To the extent any provision of this Privacy Policy is found by a competent tribunal to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be severed to the extent necessary for the remainder to be valid and enforceable.
